The energy that we be seeing with y'all is the same energy that we've been seeing with them.
Don't believe me? Just watch!
I'm trying to make a living here. Can you fuck off?
Are the kids being **** in Gaza? Is that okay?
Yeah. Hi.
**** Charleston.
You think it's funny that Israel's **** innocent lives in Gaza?
We **** your babies, yeah.
You think it's funny?
Yeah, it's very funny.
Are you even human?
I'm human. You see, I'm not robot. **** these babies.
King and other demonstrators were struck by bricks and bottles.
Do it, please.
Watch me, punk!
Motherfucker!
You ain't good enough for a real job, huh?
You're aware that a Negro family has moved into Levittown?
Yes. I heard about it.
What was your reaction?
Dynamite!
Don't finish my sentence!
No, I don't finish because you need to respect me!
Get out of here.
You can't put her out of here.
What?
Oh, spit on me again!
I've been in many demonstrations all across the South,
but I can say that I have never seen, even in Mississippi and Alabama,
mob as hostile and as hate-filled as I've seen in Chicago.
Same energy. Same.
Mm-hmm.
...